{
    "subject": "resource/Robert_Scholes",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Robert Scholes",
    "human_readable": "The label of Robert Scholes is 'Robert Scholes'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9397088289260864,
            "question": "Who is Robert Scholes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9157277345657349,
            "question": "What is the significance of Robert Scholes's label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8825225234031677,
            "question": "What is Robert Scholes known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8198338747024536,
            "question": "Is there more information available about Robert Scholes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7652757167816162,
            "question": "What field is Robert Scholes associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.749072790145874,
            "question": "Are there any notable achievements of Robert Scholes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7457250356674194,
            "question": "Where might we find more details about Robert Scholes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7063981294631958,
            "question": "Is there a connection between 'Robert Scholes' and other individuals or concepts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6979269981384277,
            "question": "Can you tell me something about Robert Scholes's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49928563833236694,
            "question": "How would you describe Robert Scholes in your own words?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Robert Scholes is 'Robert Scholes'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1066_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me something about Robert Scholes's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1066_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a connection between 'Robert Scholes' and other individuals or concepts?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1066_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might we find more details about Robert Scholes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1066_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1066_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1066_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1066_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1066_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1066_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1066_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1066_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1066_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1066_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1066_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n**Explanation:**\n\nThe provided text explicitly states \"Robert Scholes\" as his name. Therefore, the statement \"The label of Robert Scholes is 'Robert Scholes'\" is factually correct.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n* Key: \"label\"\n* Value: \"Author, Critic, Editor\"\n\nThe documents contain this information about Robert Scholes under the file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1066/re-ranker-msmarco/11.txt.\n\nSo, the answer is:\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Robert Scholes, confirming that he is indeed labeled as \"Robert Scholes.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}